Peter Sivak

email: p.sivak91@gmail.com Fairfield, CA +1-707-770-6743

(sivo91.github.io) Document (sivo91.github.io) https://peter-sivak.webs.com/

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Seeking entry level position in Web development.

Hardworking, dedicated retired professional athlete with winning attitude who delivers on goals – literally -is preparing for the next chapter in life to become front end Web developer.

My goal is to remain productive member of our family and continue to achieve success in life, to become a leader and recognized expert in a field of computer science. I believe Information Technology is going to play even greater role in our life than it does now, beyond our wildest imagination.

The past twenty years had taught me how to succeed and shine in crowd, taught me resilience and discipline. I learned to fight for every moment and learn to keep winning momentum.

My past career molded my hard-working character and righteous personality. I am used to work under pressure and deliver consistent work in the least amount of time.

These attributes allowed me to achieve success and win championships and numerous personal awards. Although, my previous career is over and it soon becomes a warm but distant memory, I look forward to a bright future and challenges that a field of computer science will bring.

QUALIFICATIONS

Web Interactivity Adobe InDesign Adobe Illustrator Photoshop C++ Fundamentals Visual Basic

Microcomputer Application

Game Coding (2d Phaser3, 3d Three.JS, 3d PlayCanvas)

Web Development1 (HTML, CSS)

Web Development2 (Bootstrap, WordPress)*current

Web Development3 (Javascript)*current

UDEMY : John Smilga(JS), Traversy Media(JS)

WORK EXPERIENCES



FedEx delivery, part-time

Daily exceeding metrics 15/ pkgs/h averaging 22 pkgs/h in the shortest time

06/12/2020 - ongoing



Professional hockey player

I was forward, yet universal -playing in all situations- on the first line, first power-play unit and killing penalties and helping the defense

I was a high scorer, yet my priority was team success -I always passed the puck to teammate who had better chance to score

I worked hard- after game or practice, I still added conditioning on the ground

EUROPE

•	HK 32 Liptovsky Mikulas	Liptovsky Mikulas, Slovakia,	09/1999 - 03/2001
•	HK Dukla Trencin	Trencin, Slovakia,	09, 2001 - 04, 2007
•	MSHK Zilina	Zilina, Slovakia,	09, 2006 - 04, 2008
•	HK Zlin	Zlin, Czech Republic,	09,2008-04,2011
•	MSHK Zilina	Zilina, Slovakia,	09/2011 - 04/2012

USA

001	-		
•	SF Bulls, ECHL	San Francisco, CA,	10/2012 - 04/2012
•	Alaska Aces, ECHL	Anchorage, AK,	10/2013 - 06/2014
•	Stockton Thunder, ECHL	Stockton, CA,	10/2014 - 01/2014
•	Orlando Solar Bears, ECHL	Orlando, FL,	02/2014 -04/2014
•	Fort Wayne Komets, ECHL	Fort Wayne, IN,	10/2015 - 12/2015
•	Alaska Aces, ECHL	Anchorage, AK,	12/2015 - 04/2016
•	Alaska Aces, ECHL	Anchorage, AK,	10/2016 - 04/2017
•	Utah Grizllies, ECHL	Salt Lake City, UT	10/2016 - 10/2016
•	Rapid City Rush, ECHL	Rapid City, SD,	10/2016 - 04/2017
•	Worchester Sharks, AHL	Worchester, MA,	03/2013 - 05/2013
•	Bridgeport Sound Tigers, AHL	Bridgeport, CT,	11/2014 - 12/2014
•	Tulsa Oilers, ECHL	Tulsa, OK,	10/2018 - 04/2019

CANADA

Abbotsford Heat, AHL
Abbotsford
09/2013 – 10/2013



Assistant coach

Recording, analyzing, highlighting individual players stats during the game, game situations, teaching on -ice, off-ice to improve strategy to win the games

Tulsa Oilers, ECHL
Tulsa, OK,
10/2018 – 04/2019

EDUCATION

EUROPE:	Elementary School	Slovakia, EU	09/1986-05/1994
	Business Academy	Slovakia, EU	09/1994 -05/1998

USA: GED Tulsa, OK and Napa, CA 2019

Full time student (**Completed 57.5 Units, current GPA = 4.00**)

Web Development Solano Community College, Fairfield, Ca 2020 – ongoing Web Development Santa Rosa Junior College Santa Rosa, Ca 2020 – ongoing

LANGUAGES

English – good Slovak – excellent Czech -- excellent

AWARDS

Slovak Extraliga National Champion	1 st Place EU	2003 - 2004
Slovak Extraliga	3 rd Place EU	2004 - 2005
Slovak Extraliga	2 nd Place EU	2006 - 2007

ECHL Kelly Cup Champion ALASKA Aces 1st Place, USA 2013 – 2014

Personal awards

ECHL Performer of the Year (+49)

ECHL Sportsmanship Award (10 PM)- honors the player judged "to have exhibited the best type of sportsmanship and gentlemanly conduct with a high standard of playing ability."

ECHL ALL-STAR Team 2015 - 2016 ECHL ALL-STAR Team NHL network televised game 2016 - 2017

LINKS

sivo91 (Peter) (github.com)

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter Siv%C3%A1k

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MYR07WEBbPg

https://www.eliteprospects.com/player/34714/peter-sivak

https://www.hockeydb.com/ihdb/stats/pdisplay.php?pid=57465

CURIOSITY

The scorer of one of the fastest goals in hockey history. 4:08

The fastest goal in Hockey,00:04:08 sec. Peter Sivak - YouTube